<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Basic_DealChicken</letterhead>
    <name>24 hours after run date - From Opp</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Congratulations on a successful DealChicken.com promotion!</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi {!Opportunity.SA_Contact_Name__c},

Congratulations on the successful &quot;hatching&quot; of {!Opportunity.Account}’s DealChicken promotion. We appreciate your decision to partner with us and are sending this quick email to highlight three important DealChicken reminders.


1. It is because of businesses like yours that DealChicken is able to provide customers amazing savings. So, we want to remind you that as your Merchant Loyalty Team, we are here to assist you in any way possible.


2. There are three ways to redeem DealChicken vouchers:



a. Online at https://www.admin.dealchicken.com and type in voucher number

b. Go to www.dealchicken.com, login and select the “vendor” option in the drop menu

c. Good ole’ pen and paper


3. The DealChicken payment structure (which is outlined in the agreement form) is one of the most business friendly out there. As a reminder:



a. Initial payments are based on sales of your promotion during its first 7 days on our site (referred to as the &quot;initial&quot; period). You will receive 70% of the payment for your week one sales in a single check, roughly 12 days after your promotion starts running. You will receive the remaining 30% approximately 25 business days after your first payment.


b. For promotions running longer than 7 days, you will receive a monthly payment on or about the 15th of the following calendar month, less a 10% holdback. The holdback will be paid (excluding any refunds) as part of your next month&apos;s payment, until there is no longer a balance.



It is our goal to provide you with eggstraordinary merchant service. Please contact us if you have any questions.



Kind Regards,

The DealChicken Merchant Team</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
</EmailTemplate>
