<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>Target Gift Card</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Target gift card for 15 minutes of your time</subject>
    <textOnly>$15 Target Gift Card for 15 Minutes of Your Time
Learn How to Find Local Customers
Quantities are Limited so Schedule Today
www.gannettlocal.com/giftcard

Hi {!Lead.FirstName}, 

We know you are busy, but we would like 15 minutes of your time to introduce you to the techniques that businesses like {!Lead.Company} are using to attract new local customers. There is no cost to you and you will receive a $15 Target gift card just by scheduling and attending a brief live presentation. 

Just click here to set up a convenient time: http://www.gannettlocal.com/giftcard 

As part of the media company that owns Arizona Republic and USA Today, GannettLocal belongs to a rich history of targeting local consumers in the places where they go for information. And now we&apos;re bringing small and medium sized businesses a proven set of online tools that help people find your business on the web - where they are already spending time. 

In just a few minutes, we can show you how to harness the power of the internet to:

*Appear on the first page of Google search results 
*Drive new visitors to your website without spending hundreds on advertising 
*Send your customers timely promotions and event notices 
*Spread brand awareness through free social media tools  

To learn more - and get your free gift card - contact me today or schedule a no-obligation overview of local marketing essentials today at http://www.gannettlocal.com/giftcard. 


&quot;Previous local marketing solutions didn&apos;t narrow my audience down to a relevant group that would actually be in need of my services.&quot;
-Chris Brown, Owner, Brandi Carpet, Gilbert 

 



 
 © 2010 Gannett Local. All rights reserved.
Target® is not affiliated with GannettLocal. Target does not sponsor, endorse, approve or have any responsibility for this promotion. The Bullseye Design and Target are registered trademarks and Target GiftCard is a service mark of Target Brands, Inc. All rights reserved. Terms and conditions are applied to GiftCards. Target is not a participating partner in or sponsor of this offer.		

 
Gannett Local 
200 E. Van Buren Street, MC 10, Phoenix, AZ, 85004, USA
http://www.gannettlocal.com/privacy-policy/</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
</EmailTemplate>
