<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Automated Proof Letter for Anthony Pamplin</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>MLC: Anthony Pamplin- Proof Letter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>*IMPORTANT* DealChicken Proof Needs Approval</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {!echosign_dev1__SIGN_Agreement__c.echosign_dev1__Account__c},

Thank you for partnering with DealChicken.com to provide customers a great offer. I am the DealChicken area manager that will be handling your promotion and I’ll be your contact to ensure your feature goes smoothly.


You&apos;re deal is scheduled to run {!echosign_dev1__SIGN_Agreement__c.DC_Run_Date__c}


Next Steps:

Our professional writing team will carefully craft the language of your promotion to get you great results based on our research and experience as a media company.
Once your proof is ready, we’ll need you to approve the proof within 24 hours so we can finalize your offer and supporting promotion.
If you are running a promotion with another daily deal site, please let me know. We want to make sure that both deals can perform their best.

Prior to your offer going live, you can visit our merchant site for guidance on preparing for a successful promotion. Please let me know if you have any questions.

Have a great day!

{!DealChicken_Project__c.Handler__c}
{!echosign_dev1__SIGN_Agreement__c.DC_MLC_Name__c},  {!echosign_dev1__SIGN_Agreement__c.DC_MLC_Location__c}
{!echosign_dev1__SIGN_Agreement__c.DC_MLC_Email__c}
{!echosign_dev1__SIGN_Agreement__c.DC_MLC_Phone__c}


How will I know who purchases my deal?
After your deal starts, you&apos;ll receive a full report with the number of deals sold, a checklist of buyers and 		total revenue.

When will I receive payment?
Expect your first payment70% of your share of the deal&apos;s revenuefive business days after the deal ends if you&apos;ve chosen direct-deposit. If you&apos;ve chosen to receive a check, this process can take up to three weeks. The balance payment (excluding refunds, if any) will be processed 25 business days after your deal closes.


Merchant Site : About | Successes | Resources | Coop News</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
</EmailTemplate>
